<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on SiliconForest RC3 Nowhere</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on SiliconForest RC3 Nowhere</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:28:34 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Insecam</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/insecam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:28:34 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/insecam/</guid><description/><content/></item><item><title>Kve</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/kve/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:26:47 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/kve/</guid><description>KVE? There was a CVE, short of Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures, a public database of disclosed computer security flaws. It benefits many system administrators and security researchers by sharing the known vulnerability and helping them to fix those holes.
And, Korean government thought, they want to have one, but they thought sharing that information publically will cause many troubles. So, they built the vulnerability database called KVE but keep its content secret, even its abstract information such as severity, impact, type of vulnerability.</description><content>&lt;h1 id="kve">KVE?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>There was a CVE, short of Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures, a public database of disclosed computer security flaws. It benefits many system administrators and security researchers by sharing the known vulnerability and helping them to fix those holes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And, Korean government thought, they want to have one, but they thought sharing that information publically will cause many troubles. So, they built the vulnerability database called KVE but keep its content secret, even its abstract information such as severity, impact, type of vulnerability.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a result, the benefit of a shared vulnerability database does not exist in KVE. Security researchers waste time writing reports about duplicated vulnerabilities because they do not have access to the database. End-users and system administrators are unable to know what threat they are currently exposed because the information is kept secret.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Their existence is only known to researchers through the KISA bug bounty program, which replies to the researcher&amp;rsquo;s mail with their useless database reference ID.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>K Security Programs</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-security-programs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 04:12:39 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-security-programs/</guid><description/><content/></item><item><title>K Builtin Iot</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-builtin-iot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 02:37:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-builtin-iot/</guid><description>Security of Korean built-in home automation system In South Korea, lots of new apartments are high-grade IT infrastructure certified. This certification requires the house has the following facilities by default:
Direct fibre-optic connection to the home Home automation system Built-in Wi-Fi access point and more things that are not so much important in this context
As a result, lots of construction companies install those systems by default. The problem is, the devices' firmware security is not examined at all and, most of them are left unmaintained, unpatched for decades.</description><content>&lt;h1 id="security-of-korean-built-in-home-automation-system">Security of Korean built-in home automation system&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>In South Korea, lots of new apartments are high-grade IT infrastructure certified. This certification requires the house has the following facilities by default:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Direct fibre-optic connection to the home
Home automation system
Built-in Wi-Fi access point
and more things that are not so much important in this context&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a result, lots of construction companies install those systems by default. The problem is, the devices' firmware security is not examined at all and, most of them are left unmaintained, unpatched for decades.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="problems-in-the-home-automation-system">Problems in the home automation system&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="always-trusts-internal-network">Always trusts internal network.&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The built-in home automation system fully trusts the internal network. The control server sends the command without any authentication or encryption and, the home automation controller accepts the connection if it has a &amp;ldquo;valid&amp;rdquo; IP address. They do not care it is spoofed or not.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a result, every room can send a spoofed packet to control someone else&amp;rsquo;s home automation system.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="no-one-is-listening-to-the-ism-band-right">No one is listening to the ISM band. Right?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Lots of Korean built-in home automation system has integrated RF transmitter which opens the entrance door. So it must be designed with security in mind. Right?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, lots of them just send RF signals without any anti-replay mechanism and can be replayed without much effort. Grab the SDR and replay the signal. Door unlocks.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="let-the-telnet-listen">Let the telnet listen&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>[TODO]&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>K Home Wrts</title><link>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-home-wrts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 02:35:38 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://pages.nowhere.rc3.silicon.moe/posts/k-home-wrts/</guid><description>K-Home-WRTs</description><content>&lt;h1 id="k-home-wrts">K-Home-WRTs&lt;/h1></content></item></channel></rss>